Previously on AMC's
Breaking Bad...
I knew there would be
a drop in quality,
but, 68%?
I left a viable operation,
the rest was up to you.
All along it was you!
Hank, my cancer is back.
In six months you won't have
someone to prosecute.
Here. Take it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Mariano, it's me.
I need you to get Skyler
on the line.
No, no, I need you to get
her on the phone right now.
Tell her it's urgent.
No-- What do you mean
she won't get off the phone?
I am giving you permission,
Mariano.
You make her get off the phone.
Mariano,
who is Skyler
on the phone with?
Yeah.
Okay.
Where is she?
Where's Skyler?
She just kinda left.
She didn't say
where she was going.
Skyler, my--
my head is spinning.